Guide to the Stephen Maxfield Parrish papers, 1901-2010.
Parrish, Stephen Maxfield papers, 1901-2010.
- Series V: Various Material
  - V. Rohan - "The Writing of W.B. Yeats's Deirdre: A Study of the Manuscripts" (cont.) (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - V. Rohan - "The Writing of W.B. Yeats's Deirdre: A Study of the Manuscripts" (cont.) (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - Various Correspondence (Box 9, Folder 17)
  - Hanshaw Rd. House Photos (Box 9, Folder 18)
  - Pethica - "Last Poems" (Box 9, Folder 19)
  - Pethica - Cathleen ni Houlihan (Box 9, Folder 20)
  - Pethica: Heads or Harps - Census of Manuscripts (Box 9, Folder 21)
  - Pethica - Country of the Young (Box 9, Folder 22)
  - CU Press Material - Diarmuid and Grania (Box 9, Folder 23)
  - Declan Kiely - Early Versions (Box 9, Folder 24)
  - Declan Kiely - Early Versions, 2002 (Box 9, Folder 25)
  - Collections of Poetry of Shelley, Keats, 1917, 1961 (Box 9, Folder 26)
  - SUNY Library - List of Manuscripts in the Collection of Michael Yeats (Box 9, Folder 27)
  - A Guide to Research - W.B. Yeats Microfilmed Manuscripts (Box 9, Folder 28)
  - SUNY Library - W.B. Yeats Archives, 1978-1981 (Box 9, Folder 29)
  - Yeats: Conrad Balliett Indexes (Box 9, Folder 30)
  - Resources for Irish Studies at SIU Carbondale, 1995 (Box 9, Folder 31)
  - Indexes of Manuscripts Archives (Harvard, BC, and elsewhere) (Box 9, Folder 32)
  - SUNY Library - Yeats Collection Guide, 1989 (Box 9, Folder 33)
  - White Vellum Notebook Index (Box 9, Folder 34)
  - Cornell Yeats: Original Budgets in Grant Application, 2002 (Box 9, Folder 35)
  - Gill: "Salisbury Plain", 1976-1990 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Longman Manuscript at Yale, 1956 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Stone Evening Walk, 1973-1976 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Jordan: Notes on Peter Bell, 1973-1982 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Cornell Concordance Series Papers (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - JEGP (Journal of Germanic and English Philology), 1976 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Crane: "The High Priori Road" (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Wordsworth Seminar - NEH, 1992 (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - The Georgia Review, 1981 (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Erdman: "The Binding (Et Cetera) of Vala", 1968 (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - UVA Bibliographic Society Papers, 1965 (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - The Sewanee, Kentucky, and Centennial Reviews, 1960-1968 (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - Wayne Chapman: "George Yeats, Cathleen, and P.S. O'Hegarty: Notes from the Libraries" (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - Heppner: "The Cave and the City: Wordsworth's London Revisited" (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - Various Wordsworth Essays (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - Behler: "The Theory of Irony in German Romanticism" (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - Literary Criticism Articles, 1986 (Box 10, Folder 17)
  - Assorted Publications: Various Authors (Box 10, Folder 18)
  - "Computer Applications to Problems in the Humanities" - SUNY Brockport, 1969 (Box 10, Folder 19)
  - Dugas: "White Doe" (Box 10, Folder 20)
  - "Digital Image Processing of Medieval Manuscripts" Conference - USC, 1977 (Box 10, Folder 21)
  - Sarah Hutchinson's Poets (Box 10, Folder 22)
  - Curtis: P2V (Box 10, Folder 23)
  - Wordsworth: Editor's Manual, 1991 (Box 10, Folder 24)
  - Manuscript 1827/40 - Lilly Library, Indiana, 1982 (Box 10, Folder 25)
  - "The Fire Sculpture of the Gods:" Poems by N. Dylan Willoughby (Box 10, Folder 26)
  - Cornell Office of Sponsored Programs - Guide to Budgeting and Costing of Sponsored Programs (Box 10, Folder 27)
  - Cornell Yeats: NEH Grant Applications, 1994-1998 (Box 10, Folder 28)
  - NEH Budget Forms, 1994-1996 (Box 10, Folder 29)
  - NEH - Earlier Applications, 1994-1998 (Box 10, Folder 30)
  - Cornell Yeats - Budget Forms, 2000 (Box 10, Folder 31)
  - Cornell's NEH Application (Box 10, Folder 32)
  - Cornell Yeats - NEH Application Papers (Box 10, Folder 33)
  - Cornell - Sponsored Programs and the Hull Fund, 2003 (Box 10, Folder 34)
  - Cornell Yeats - Project Description (Box 10, Folder 35)
  - The Wordsworth Collection, 1931 (Box 10, Folder 36)
  - Guggenheim Report, 2000 (Box 10, Folder 37)
  - Newspaper Articles, 1998 (Box 10, Folder 38)
  - Paper on Irony; Ch. 1 & 2 (Box 10, Folder 39)
  - Ch. 3: The Ironies of Autobiography (Box 10, Folder 40)
  - The Wordsworth Circle, 2001-2002 (Box 10, Folder 41)
  - The Wordsworth Circle, 2002-2003 (Box 10, Folder 42)
  - Periodicals - Literature Journals, 1960-1986 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Bulletin of the NY Public Library, 1960 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Symposia and Conferences, 1954-1991 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - The Wordsworth Circle, 1976, 2004, 2005 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - The Wordsworth Circle, 2003-2004 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Newspaper Articles, 2003 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Diacritics: A Review of Contemporary Criticism, 1987 (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Manual for Editors - The Cornell Wordsworth, 1991 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Photos - Yeats Manuscripts (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Coleridge Paper, 1940 (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Articles and Bulletins, 1972-1987 (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - Literature Periodicals, 1964-1978 (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - Literature Periodicals, 1960-1964 (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - Literature Periodicals, 1982 (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - J.C.C. Mays Lecture, 2003 (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - Report of the Dean of Arts & Sciences, 1968 (Box 11, Folder 16)
  - Samuel Guttman Paper on Freud (Box 11, Folder 17)
  - Sotheby's Sale & Betz Exhibition (Box 11, Folder 18)
  - Literary Data Processing Conference Proceedings, 1964 (Box 11, Folder 19)
  - Various Literary Essays (Box 11, Folder 20)
  - Cornell University Library (Box 11, Folder 21)
  - Wordsworth Love Letters - The Sotheby's Sale, 1977-1978 (Box 11, Folder 22)
  - Literary Periodicals, 1985-1998 (Box 11, Folder 23)
  - Fraternities, 1967 (Box 11, Folder 24)
  - Fraternities - Study Committee, 1967 (Box 11, Folder 25)
  - Articles - 6-Year Ph.D Students, 1958-1970 (Box 11, Folder 26)
  - Book Contracts, Royalties, 1966 (Box 11, Folder 27)
  - West Point Teaching (Box 11, Folder 28)
  - Fellowships, 1985-1989 (Box 11, Folder 29)
  - Sotheby's Purchase - Wordsworth's Poetical Works, 1998 (Box 11, Folder 30)
  - Yeats: Essays, 1995 (Box 11, Folder 31)
  - Various Yeats and Wordsworth Papers (Box 12)
  - Various Yeats and Wordsworth Papers (Box 13)
  - Sequence of papers relating to Cornell Wordsworth Series edition of The Excursion, 1974-2005 (Box 16)
  - Sequence of papers relating to Cornell Wordsworth Series edition of Lyrical Ballads, 1972-1996 (Box 16)
  - Jared Curtis Correspondence (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Jared Curtis Correspondence (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - Jared Curtis Correspondence (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Jared Curtis Correspondence (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - Jared Curtis Correspondence (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - Jared Curtis Correspondence (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - Jared Curtis Correspondence (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - Jared Curtis Correspondence (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - Recommendation of Everard King's Book "James Beattie's 'The Minstrel' and Romantic Autobiography", 1987 (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - Permission to Quote Correspondence, 1991 (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - Recommendation of Kenneth Johnston's Book "Young Wordsworth", 1996 (Box 17, Folder 11)
  - Proposal for a Cornell Wordsworth Series, 1976-1978 (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Jared Curtis Papers: "Wordsworth's Poems (1807): A Critical Edition", not dated (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Mark Reed postcard and review of The Prelude, 1971 (Box 19, Folder 14)
  - 1799 Prelude, 1974-1975 (Box 19, Folder 15)
  - Grants, 2000-2006 (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - Photographs, Date unknown (Box 22)
- Series VI: Audio/visual media
  - Yeats: Microfilm and Floppy Disks (Box 14)
  - CD-1594: “Sophocles’ Oedipus at Colonus” - by Yeats (1926-1939), edited by Jared Curtis (2007) – draft copy (Box 19)
  - CD-1595: “Sophocles’ Oedipus at Colonus” - by Yeats (1926-1939), edited by Jared Curtis (2007) – book copy (Box 19)
  - CD-1596: “At the Hawk’s Well” and “The Cat and the Moon” - by Yeats (n.d.), edited by Andrew Parkin (2008-2009) – draft copy (Box 19)
  - CD-1597 and 1598: “At the Hawk’s Well” and “The Cat and the Moon” - by Yeats (n.d.), edited by Andrew Parkin (2008-2009) – book copy (Box 19)
  - CD-1599 contains: (Box 19)
    “Diarmuid and Grania” – by Yeats and George Moore (n.d.), edited by J. C. C. Mays - intro
    “The Only Jealousy of Emer” – untranscribed version
    “The Only Jealousy of Emer” and “Fight the Waves” - by Yeats (1917-1934), edited by Steven Winnett (2003) – book copy
  - CD-1600: “The Only Jealousy of Emer” and “Fight the Waves” – by Yeats (1917-1934), edited by Steven Winnett (2003) - draft 5 (Box 19)
  - CD-1601: “The King’s Threshold” – by Yeats (1903-1934), edited by Declan Kiely (2004) - book copy (Box 19)
  - CD-1602: “The Golden Helmet” and “The Green Helmet” – by Yeats (1908-1934), edited by William Hogan (2008) (Box 19)
  - CD-1603: “The Resurrection” – by Yeats (1925-1934), edited by Selina Guinness and Jared Curtis (2010) (Box 19)
  - CD-1604: “The King and the Great Clock Tower” and “A Full Moon in March” – by Yeats (1934-1935), edited by Richard Allen Cave (2006) – draft and review copy (Box 19)
  - CD-1605: “The King and the Great Clock Tower” and “A Full Moon in March” – by Yeats (1934-1935), edited by Richard Allen Cave (2006) – review copy (Box 19)
  - CD-1606: “The Tower” – by Yates (1928), edited by Richard L. Finneran (2004) – review copy (Box 19)
  - CD-1607: “The Tower” – by Yates (1928), edited by Richard L. Finneran (2004) – review copy (Box 19)
  - CD-1608 contains: (Box 19)
    Bodleian Library, University of Oxford material (2004)
    Census of manuscripts for “The Tower” (2004)
    Curtis/Finneran correspondence (2004)
    Curtis/Mays correspondence (2004)
    “The Tower” (2004) – review copy
  - CD-1609: “Collaborative one act plays 1901-1903: Cathleen ni Houlihan, Heads or Harps, The Country of the Young, The Pot of Broth” – by Yeats and Lady Gregory (n.d.), edited by James Pethica (2004) (Box 19)
  - CD-1610: Four Plays, correspondence and front matter (2004) (Box 19)